(0)

[\[email protected\]](https://www.therapyshoppe.com/cdn-cgi/l/email-protection)

8:00 am - 4:30 pm EST. M-F

[Login](https://www.therapyshoppe.com/login) or [Register](https://www.therapyshoppe.com/login/registration)

* [Home](https://www.therapyshoppe.com/) \> 
* Terms of Use 

Terms of Use
------------

**WELCOME TO THE THERAPY SHOPPE!** Therapyshoppe.com (the "Site") offers a variety of merchandise for purchase online (collectively the "Products"). By accessing the Site and/or purchasing any Product, you agree to be bound by the following terms and conditions (the "Terms of Use"), as well as our Privacy Policy (incorporated here by reference) and all other applicable laws, statutes, ordinances and regulations concerning your access of the Site and/or purchase of a Product. We may revise these Terms of Use at any time by posting revised terms on this Site and such revised terms take immediate effect. Please note that it is your responsibility to check these Terms of Use before each purchase of a Product.

**YOUR RESPONSIBILITIES, REGISTRATION OBLIGATIONS, AND MEMBERSHIP ACCOUNT:** In order to purchase Products, you will be required to provide complete and accurate information when requested. Users on the Site are required to formally accept these Terms of Use. You will have the option of registering on the Site and creating a formal account. As a User, you are responsible to maintain the confidentiality of your password and/or login information, and for restricting access to your computer. You agree to accept responsibility for all activities that occur under your account or password. If you are under 18, you may use our website only with involvement of a parent of guardian. Therapy Shoppe®, Incorporated and its associates reserve the right to refuse service, terminate accounts, remove or edit content, or cancel orders in their sole discretion.

**PRICE/DESCRIPTION CHANGES OR OMISSIONS:** The content of the website, including but not limited to: text, pricing, availability, graphics, and descriptions may contain errors or inaccuracies, and may not always be complete or current. All materials are subject to changing without notice. Therapyshoppe.com reserves the right to correct any errors, inaccuracies, or omissions, and also reserves the right to change or update any information at any time without prior notice.

**ORDERING TERMS AND POLICIES:** [Click here](https://www.therapyshoppe.com/ordering-info#payment) to review the therapyshoppe.com Order Terms and Policies which are incorporated here by reference.

**PRIVACY POLICY:** [Click here](#privacypolicy) to review the therapyshoppe.com Privacy Policy which is incorporated here by reference.

**INTELLECTUAL PROPERTY:** You acknowledge and agree that the Site, the Products, and the content of the Site (including the content, format, graphics, text, typefaces, imagery, other materials on the website) are protected by proprietary rights throughout the world, including but not limited to copyrights, trademarks, trade secrets, service marks or patents (called "Intellectual Property Rights"). These Intellectual Property Rights are valid and protected in all forms, media and technologies existing now or developed later. All rights, title and interest in and to the Site, the Products, and such content, including but not limited to all Intellectual Property Rights, belong solely and exclusively to the owners of Therapy Shoppe®, Inc./therapyshoppe.com or its licensors. Nothing contained in this Site should be construed as granting, by implication, estoppel or otherwise, any license or use rights in or to the Site, the Products or Content. All content included on this site, such as text, graphics, logos, button icons, images, digital downloads, data compilations, and software, is the property of Therapy Shoppe, Inc®. or its content suppliers, and is copyrighted as a collective work under U.S. and international copyright laws. The Company owns a copyright in the selection, coordination, arrangement, and enhancement of such Content. You agree that no part of the Site may be copied, reproduced, transmitted, displayed, duplicated, uploaded, downloaded, or modified in any way without prior written consent of the owners of the Therapy Shoppe, Inc®. Therapy Shoppe, Inc®. reserves the complete title and full intellectual property rights for materials downloaded from the Website, with the exception that you may may download or print one copy of the materials on any single computer for personal, non-commercial use only, provided you keep intact all copyright, trademark, and other proprietary notices. Modification of the materials or use of the materials for any other purpose is a violation of Therapy Shoppe, Incorporated's Intellectual property rights. Unauthorized duplication is a violation of law.

**LICENSE AND SITE ACCESS:** Therapy Shoppe®, Inc. grants you a limited license to access and make personal use (only) of this site, and not to modify it, or any portion of it, except with written consent of Therapy Shoppe® Inc. This license does not include any resale or commercial use of this site or its contents: any collection and use of any product listings, descriptions, or prices: any derivative use of this site or its contents: any downloading or copying of account information or the benefit of another merchant: or any use of data mining, robots, or similar data gathering and extraction tools. This site or any portion of this site may not be reproduced, duplicated, copied, sold, visited, or other exploited for any commercial purpose without express written consent of Therapy Shoppe® Inc. You may not frame or utilize framing techniques to enclose any trademark, logo, or other proprietary information (including images, text, page layout, or form) of Therapy Shoppe® and our associates without expressed written consent. You may not use any meta tags or any other hidden text: utilizing Therapy Shoppe® name or trademarks without the express written consent of Therapy Shoppe®. Any unauthorized use terminates the permission or license granted by Therapy Shoppe®. You are granted a limited, revocable, and nonexclusive right to create a hyperlink to the home page of Therapy Shoppe® as long as the link does not portray Therapy Shoppe® or any of its associates, or their products or services in a false, misleading, derogatory, or otherwise offensive matter. You may not use any Therapy Shoppe® logo or other proprietary graphic or trademark as part or the link without express written permission.

This site is owned and operated by Therapy Shoppe®, Inc. ("Therapy Shoppe").

**DISCLAIMER OF WARRANTIES: THE SITE AND ITS CONTENT IS PROVIDED "AS IS," WITH NO WARRANTIES WHATSOEVER. THERAPY SHOPPE, INC. EXPRESSLY DISCLAIMS TO THE FULLEST EXTENT PERMITTED BY LAW ALL EXPRESS, IMPLIED, AND STATUTORY WARRANTIES, INCLUDING, WITHOUT LIMITATION, THE WARRANTIES OF MERCHANTABILITY, FITNESS FOR A PARTICULAR PURPOSE, AND NON-INFRINGEMENT OF PROPRIETARY RIGHTS. THERAPY SHOPPE, INC. DOES NOT WARRANT THAT ACCESS TO THE SITE WILL BE UNINTERRUPTED OR FREE FROM ANY VIRUSES OR OTHER DISABLING CODE.**

**LIMITATION OF LIABILITY: UNDER NO CIRCUMSTANCES SHALL THERAPY SHOPPE, INC. BE LIABLE TO ANY USER ON ACCOUNT OF THE USE OR MISUSE OF, OR RELIANCE ON THE SITE OR ANY PRODUCT. THIS LIMITATION OF LIABILITY PREVENTS RECOVERY OF DIRECT, INDIRECT, INCIDENTAL, CONSEQUENTIAL, SPECIAL EXEMPLARY, AND PUNITIVE DAMAGES WHETHER SUCH CLAIM IS BASED ON WARRANTY, CONTRACT, TORT (INCLUDING NEGLIGENCE), OR OTHERWISE. SUCH LIMITATION SHALL APPLY TO THE FULLEST EXTENT PERMITTED BY LAW.**

**INDEMNIFICATION:** You agree to indemnify, defend, and hold us, Therapy Shoppe, Inc. (and our affiliates, related parties, officers, directors, employees, agents, independent contractors, advertisers, partners, and co-branders) harmless, from financial liabilities associated with any and all claims or demands, including reasonable attorney's fees, that may be made by any third party, that arises from or relates to your use of this Site or the Products or your violation of these Terms of Service.

**FORCE MAJEURE:** Therapy Shoppe, Inc. will not be liable in any amount for failure to perform under this Agreement if such failure is caused by power outages, Internet outages, communications outages, fire, flood, earthquakes, tornadoes, war, acts of God, terrorist acts or the occurrence of any other unforeseen contingency beyond the control of Therapy Shoppe, Inc.

**MISCELLANEOUS PROVISIONS:** These Terms of Use will be governed by and construed in accordance with the laws of the State of Michigan, without giving effect to its conflict of laws provisions or your actual state or country of residence. You consent and submit to the exclusive jurisdiction and venue of the federal and states courts sitting in Kent County, Michigan. Any cause of action you may have with respect to your use of the Site must be commenced within one (1) year after the claim or cause of action arises.

These Terms of Use constitute the entire agreement between the parties with respect to the subject matter hereof and supersede and replace all prior or contemporaneous understandings or agreements, written or oral, regarding such subject matter.

Any waiver of any provision of the Terms of Use will be effective only if such waiver is in writing and signed by one of our authorized representatives. Our waiver of any provision of these Terms of Service or of a breach by you of any provision of these Terms of Use shall not be deemed a waiver of future compliance with these Terms of Use and such provision, as well as all other provisions of these Terms of Use, shall remain in full force and effect.

If, for any reason, a court of competent jurisdiction finds any provision of the Terms of Use to be unenforceable, the remainder of the Terms of Use will continue in full force and effect.

PRIVACY POLICY
--------------

At therapyshoppe.com (the "Site"), we respect your privacy and are firmly committed to protecting it when you visit our website. We will not sell, rent, lease, share, or disclose your personal information (name, email address, telephone or fax numbers, address, or credit numbers) to any third parties, except as set forth in this Privacy Policy.

This Privacy Policy outlines the types of personal information we gather when you use the Site or its services, as well as some of the steps we take to safeguard it.

The following principles apply to the personally identifying information we ask for and that you provide. "Personally identifying information" is information that individually identifies you, such as your name, physical address, email address, telephone number, or credit card information.

**DATA COLLECTION:** Using some of our services may require that you register with a user name. Any user who registers with the site is considered a "registered user." We will ask you for some personal information in order to create an account (typically your name, email address, and a password for your account), and we will use that information to provide the service. Any user purchasing products from the Site will also be required to provide credit card information.

**COOKIES:** We use "cookies" to collect certain bits of technical and navigational information that allows us to keep track of the contents of your shopping cart and tells us how you use our site (such as pages visited, etc). This information may be used to resolve technical issues, or be analyzed to improve our website functionality so we can serve you better! We do not collect or store personally identifiable information.

**INFORMATION SHARING:** We only share information under the following circumstances:

\--We may share the information submitted under your account with our business partners for order fulfillment and warranty issues (examples would be: processing your credit card information with VISA or Mastercard services or submitting your package/tracking information to UPS or the Postal Service as we process your order, etc). We will not disclose your account information to non-affiliated people or companies, except in the limited circumstances described in this Policy above.

\--We conclude that we are required by law or have a good faith belief that access, preservation or disclosure of such information is reasonably necessary to protect the rights, property or safety of the Site, its users or the public.

**ACCESS:** If you want to see the personal identifying information we have collected about you from this website or if you believe any information we have is incorrect and you wish to correct it, please contact us at the e-mail address or phone number provided below. If we change or delete information in response to your request, we will not then continue to use it; however, some residual information may remain in backup records or records of deletions.

**INFORMATION SECURITY:** Protecting your privacy and your information is a top priority. We take appropriate measures to secure both your information and our physical premises. We exercise reasonable care in providing safe transmission of your information from your PC to our servers (unless sent by a means outside of our control, such as e-mail). We utilize industry standard secure software (SSL), encrypted storage and password protection systems, etc. However, we cannot guarantee that our measures will completely bar unauthorized access to your information, and by using the Site you assume this risk.

**CHILDREN:** Children under the age of 13 should not send any information about themselves to us, including information like your name, address or e-mail address. The Site does not knowingly collect personally identifying information from children under the age of 13. In the event that we learn that we have collected such information from a child under 13 without parental consent, the information will be deleted from our database as soon as reasonably possible.

**CHANGES TO THIS POLICY:** Please note this Privacy Policy will change from time to time. We will post those changes on this page and, if the changes are significant, we will also provide a more prominent notice. Therefore you should review the Site's Privacy Policy for potential changes when you return to the web site for future visits.

**CONSENT TO TRANSFER:** This site is operated in the United States. If you are located in the European Union or elsewhere outside of the United States, please be aware that any information you provide to us will be transferred to the United States. By using our website, participating in any of our services and/or providing us with your information, you consent to this transfer.

Communications regarding this Privacy Policy should be directed to: This email address is being protected from spambots. You need JavaScript enabled to view it. or by calling (800) 261-5590. This Site is owned and operated by Therapy Shoppe® Inc., PO Box 230, Rockford, MI 49341.

### Customer Care

### My Account

### Sales and Gift Center

Copyright © 1996 - 2024 [Therapy Shoppe®, Inc. All rights reserved.](https://www.therapyshoppe.com/ "Therapy Shoppe®, Inc. All rights reserved.")

Therapy Shoppe® Inc., PO Box 230 Rockford MI 49341
